[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term refers to the horizontal line, 23.5 degrees S, which passes through South America, Africa, and Australia?", "correct_answer": "Tropic of Capricorn", "incorrect_answers": ["Tropic of Cancer", "Prime Meridian", "Equator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sequel to the 2003 movie Bruce Almighty was released in 2007?", "correct_answer": "Evan Almighty", "incorrect_answers": ["Vincent Almighty", "Trevor Almighty", "Grace Almighty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are CDs and DVDs read?", "correct_answer": "Laser", "incorrect_answers": ["Sensor", "Beam of Nuclear Radiation", "Magnetically"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the robot repairing on the outside of the ship in the movie WALL-E?", "correct_answer": "a light", "incorrect_answers": ["a door", "the deck", "He wasnt fixing anything, he was on a break."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elvis Presley, often referred to as the King of Rock and Roll, was born in which southern state?", "correct_answer": "Mississippi", "incorrect_answers": ["Alabama", "Tennessee", "North Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Colonel Billy Mitchell appear in a Walt Disney full length animated film?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the former name of the city of Istanbul ?", "correct_answer": "Constantinople", "incorrect_answers": ["Persia", "Zaire", "Siam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the highest layer of the Earth\u2019s atmosphere?", "correct_answer": "Exosphere", "incorrect_answers": ["Iconosphere", "Ectosphere", "Endosphere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many keys are on a piano?", "correct_answer": "88", "incorrect_answers": ["56", "80", "98"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the first spacecraft that visited Neptune?", "correct_answer": "Voyager 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Voyager 1", "Pioneer 10", "Pioneer 11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dinosaurs once roamed Colorado and Wyoming.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does WALL-E find the plant in the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "In a refrigerator", "incorrect_answers": ["In a trash can", "In a storm shelter", "In a greenhouse"]}]